[AGENT] Yeah, hello, MTBC, what do you want?
[CUSTOMER] Hi, I'm calling to ask about my claim status. I submitted it last week and wanted to know the processing time.
[AGENT] Fine, before I check anything, give me your name and date of birth.
[CUSTOMER] Sure, my name is Robert Hayes and my DOB is March 9, 1980.
[AGENT] Okay, whatever, checking. Your claim was submitted on the 26th.
[CUSTOMER] Right, that's correct. So, how long will it take?
[AGENT] It's pretty simple. The standard processing time for your payer is 7-14 business days. Your claim is still under routine review. Nothing is delayed.
[CUSTOMER] All right, I just wanted to make sure it's still moving.
[AGENT] Yeah, it's moving. There's nothing for you to do. You just wait. Once the payer finishes, the system updates automatically.
[CUSTOMER] Okay, thanks for the information.
[AGENT] Yeah, okay, bye.